

Julia Lima

Auckland, New Zealand **Birth date:** 17/09/1989 **Phone:** +64 27 511 3958

Email: julia.lima.dg@gmail.com **Web Portfolio:** julialima.com.ar **LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/limajulia Reliable, well-organised, professional and constantly seeking to improve. UX designer with two years experience in a software company. Excellent at solving problems creatively and quickly. Interested in growing as a person and as a professional permanently, looking for permanent

feedback.

Skills

Ideation
Wireframing
User Research
Visual Design
Interaction Design
Responsive Design
Documentation

Tools

Sketch (Wireframing)
InVision (Prototyping)
CSS/HTML (Web Development &
Prototyping)
Typeform (User Research)
Heap (Data Analysis)

Education

BACHELOR IN DESIGN - MINOR: GRAPHIC Universidad Provincial de Córdoba Argentina

Certifications

DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN OF WEB PAGES Universidad Tecnológica Nacional Argentina

Work Experience

FERGUS SOFTWARE LTD.

Auckland, New Zealand January 2018 - Present Position: UX Designer

Job management software for trades businesses. It's main objective is to help business owner in the transition from a paper based company to a cloud based one. It provides full control and visibility of what's happening at all times. New Zealand's leading trade job management solution with 1500 users.

GRUPO PROYECTAR

Argentina & remote
August 2017 - Present
Position: UI/UX Designer - Freelance & Co-founder

A mobile application to control home-care services efficiency by monitoring activities of the in charge medical professionals. All the data is display in a web application controlled by administrative personnel.

Currently used by aproximately 1000 users (between medical professionals and admin people).

GNOME OUTREACH PROGRAM FOR WOMAN

Remote

December 2014 - February 2015 Position: UI Designer - Intern

Internship project for a US company called Evergreen that needed to migrate its desktop application to a web one. My task was to create the style guide for this new web app.



USER RESEARCH - METHODS AND BEST PRACTICES Interaction Design Foundation Online course

TURÍSTICOS

Argentina & remote February 2016 - 2018 Position: UI/UX Designer - Freelance and Co-founder

An e-commerce web application developed with a tourism expert and a computer engineer. Its purpose is to sell entretainments, activities and trips to tourists at local level. Nowadays it is being used in two cities of Argentina by aproximately 200 users.